DAYS!
By the decision of Ying Zheng, the king that wished to unite all of China,
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
天下統一の道を行く王 嬴政(えいせい)のもと
the State of Qin began its invasion of the State of Wei.
秦国(しんこく)は 魏国(ぎこく)へと侵攻した
立ちはだかる敵は
伝説の大将軍 廉頗(れんぱ)
The enemy blocking their way is the legendary Great General, Lian Po.
Young generals take on this relentless battlefield in hopes of rendering great military achievements.
若き将たちは 大いなる武功を狙い
この苛烈な戦場に挑む
（地響き）
（尾平(びへい)）この音って まさか あの…
Th-This sound. Don't tell me it's...
Y-Yeah...
（澤圭(たくけい)）は… はい！
This ain't good.
（沛浪(はいろう)）マズイ！
The State of Wei's armored chariots!
魏国の装甲戦車だ！
Dammit!
（信(しん)）
しまった！ そこの歩兵 逃げろ！
Foot soldiers over there, run!
（信）
クッ… よりによって戦車が…
Damn, now chariots of all things...
Protect the captain!
（楚水(そすい)）隊長を守れ！
俺は いい！
それよりも歩兵たちを！
I'll be fine!
Focus on the foot soldiers!
ンンッ… この煙に戦車…
Chariots in this smoke...
どうする？ どうやって…
What do we do?! How do we...?!
（羌瘣(きょうかい)）信！
（信）ああ？
Xin.
Just one...
（羌瘣）ひとつだけ…
（信）うん？
I have one plan.
（羌瘣）ひとつだけ策がある
The Feixin Unit's Counterattack
In addition, there is a certain pleasant feeling in battles I know no substitute for.
（玄峰(げんぽう)）ほかには代え難い快感が
戦にはある
And that is for a strategist to use his lone brain to operate 10,000 men to carry out an overwhelming slaughter.
（玄峰）軍略家にとって―
それは 己の脳ひとつで
万人の戦いを操作し
一方的に殺戮(さつりく)することじゃ
Truly as he described it,
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）正に その言葉どおり―
Xuan Feng's technique was that of manipulating the battlefield like he would pieces on a game board
玄峰の戦術は 盤上の遊びのごとく
戦場を操るものであり
and efficiently inter the State of Qin soldiers.
効率的に秦国兵を葬るものであった
With the battlefield in chaos under the smokescreen, he placed soldiers across the battlefield in order to divide it into sections.
乱戦を行っていた魏国兵は
煙幕の中―
戦場全体を いくつもの区画に
分けるように配置に就いた
次に 弓隊は
秦国兵に打撃を与えながらも―
Then, as the bow unit delivered strikes to the State of Qin soldiers,
実は
彼らが直線上に密集するよう誘導し
they were actually concentrating their shots in a straight line
戦車隊は 秦国兵で
埋め尽くされた その道を爆走した
in order to guide the Chariot Corps to rush down that path full of Qin soldiers.
Of course, surrounded by smoke, the State of Qin soldiers knew nothing about this.
当然 煙の中にいる秦国兵たちは
この状況を全く分かっておらず
次々 現れる戦車の攻撃を
ただただ受けるだけであった
They had no choice but to defend against the chariot attacks coming one after another.
Unable to understand anything from within that huge smokescreen,
内外から
うかがい知れぬ この大煙幕の中
the State of Qin Army amassed a horrific number of casualties.
秦国軍は 恐ろしいほどの
死傷者の山を築いていたのである
Qiang Lei, what's your plan?!
羌瘣 策って何だ？
（戦車の音）
（渕(えん)･楚水）あっ！
（戦車兵）ヌオーッ！
Jump!
（信）飛べ！
うらぁ！
（斬る音）
（戦車兵）ウワッ！
Lord Xin!
（渕）信どの！
（楚水）守りを固めろ！
信どのを中心にだ！
Tighten the guard!
Center around Lord Xin!
We make noise to confuse them.
（羌瘣）音を発して 攪乱(かくらん)する
（信）うん？
Every once in a while you can hear this high-pitched bell ringing, right?
時折 聞こえる甲高い鐘の音が
あるだろう
They're using that to tell the bow unit or the chariot unit where we are.
弓隊や戦車隊に
我々の位置を教えている
（鐘の音）
あっ 音の拍子か！
A sound signal?!
Yes. So if we create a sound similar to that one from where we are,
そうだ
これに似た音をこちらから発して
we can throw their communication out of order.
そのやり取りを妨害する
フフッ… よし！
Okay.
まずは みんなに
これに近い音を出す物を探させて
First, we need everyone to find everything nearby that's making that sound and cut them all down!
ガンガン打たせろ！
（戦場に響く音）
今 気づいたのですが…
I've only just realized this, but there is also a different lower, echoing sound...
また別に低く響く音が…
What in the world... Is this another signal?
これは 一体… これも合図か？
That's a gong.
ドラの音だな
本陣からの合図だろう きっと
It's a signal coming from the headquarters.
They're probably sending some bigger signal.
もっと大きな指示を送っている
ハッ… 羌瘣！
Qiang Lei!
Did you just say it's a signal from the headquarters?!
お前 今
“本陣からの合図”っつったか？
Which means... in other words...
てことは つまり…
この音を発してる場所に―
the place this sound is coming from
is where the enemy headquarters is, ain't it?!
敵の本陣が
あるってことじゃねえのか？
Could it be...?!
He's planning to target the headquarters...?!
まさか…
本陣を狙う気か？
Forget it.
ムリだ
この煙と騒音の中
With all this smoke and noise
it's not possible to locate the origin of this gong sound.
あのドラの音を発している所を
特定することはできない
Qiang Lei. Don't tell me you forgot...
羌瘣 忘れてねえか？
about them?
あいつらのことを
You called, Captain?
（石(せき)）呼んだか？ 隊長
The Qingshi Clan!
（渕）青石(せいせき)族！
石！ 山で暮らしているお前らは
絶対 俺たちより耳がいい
Shi! Having grown up in the mountains, you've definitely got better ears than any of us!
If any of you can tell where that gong sound is coming from,
あのドラを鳴らしてる場所が
分かるヤツがいるか―
仲間に聞いてくれ
tell all of us!
You need not even ask.
（石）聞くまでもない
They call me the one with the ears that grasp the flapping of wings.
我が名は
〝羽音をつかむ耳〞
Shen Chief
Shi
If that is where you want to go,
そこに行きたいのなら
一族で いちばんの耳を
持つ私が案内してやろう
allow me, who possesses the best
ears in our clan, to guide you.
Okay.
よし！
騎馬隊だけで行く！ 楚水 集めろ！
Just the mounted unit will go!
Chu Shui, gather them!
渕さん
悪いが ここで歩兵隊の指揮を頼む
Mr. Yuan, sorry, but I'm gonna need you here to direct the foot soldiers.
（渕）承知しました
（信）うん
Understood.
（楚水）お… お待ちを 信どの！
Please wait, Lord Xin.
我々の騎馬隊は 集まっても150
それに対し―
Even with our mounted unit fully assembled, we have only 150.
Whereas the enemy headquarters has numbers we cannot even estimate.
敵本陣に どれだけの数がいるか
予想がつきません
If we go to the headquarters now and it turns out to be impossible to penetrate,
いざ本陣まで行って
突入が不可能になった場合
この煙の中 騎馬隊は もう
元の場所に戻ってはこられません
with this smoke everywhere, the mounted unit will not be able to get back to where we came from.
そうなったら
飛信(ひしん)隊は完全にバラバラになり
If that happens, the Feixin Unit will be completely split apart and thus in grave danger.
危機に陥ります
I think we should request mounted reinforcements!
騎馬の援軍を頼むべきです
（信）そんな のんきなこと
やってられっか！
Like we've got time to play it safe like that!
The State of Qin Army could be wiped out by the time that happens!
その間に 秦国軍は
全滅すっかもしれねえんだぞ！
But...
（楚水）しかし…
（信）楚水！
Chu Shui!
You told me, didn't you?
お前 言ったよな？
千人隊は… 千人将は―
A Thousand-Man Unit... A Thousand-Man General is something with the power to overturn the state of a battle.
戦局を覆すことができる存在だって
Now's that time!
今が その時だ！
With our hands, we'll lead our army to our first victory!
俺たちの手で
この緒戦を勝利に導くんだ！
It seems there is no use trying to stop you.
（楚水）止めてもムダのようですね
Yeah. Even if you don't go, I'll go on my own.
ああ お前らが行かなくても
俺１人でも行く
（楚水）フッ… ご冗談を
Please do not kid around.
We are the Feixin Unit.
我らは飛信隊
Where the captain goes, we go! No matter how deadly it may be!
隊長の行く所なら
どんな死地にも お供いたします
（じい）蒙恬(もうてん)さま
この第３陣は動かぬのでしょうか？
Lord Meng Tian, do you think this third formation will not be moving?
戦況は分かりませぬが
I'm not sure what the state of the battle is, but...
It's certain that they are fighting a hard battle under that smokescreen.
あの煙幕の中
苦戦しているのは必至かと
（蒙恬）難しいな
This is tricky.
Since we can't tell what's going on inside,
中の様子が見えない以上―
we can't tell where or what kind of reinforcements we should send.
どこに どう援軍を送ればいいのか
判断がつかない
But that smokescreen isn't just any ordinary smoke.
しかし
あの煙幕 ただの煙じゃないな
The fact that the State of Wei soldiers are fighting in there as well
あの中で
魏国兵も戦っているということは
窒息することがないよう
作られたものだ
means that it was made in a way that you won't suffocate in it.
An enemy that would bring out something like that is considerably skilled.
あんなものを持ち込む敵は
相当の曲者(くせもの)だ
It's likely that Grandfather isn't thinking about sending in reinforcements,
多分 じいさまは
援軍のことじゃなく
第１陣 第２陣を
退却させるかどうかを考えているよ
but rather deciding whether or not to get the first and second formations to retreat.
In each of the State of Wei's units,
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）魏国の各隊には―
there were a few soldiers which had a thorough knowledge of Xuan Feng's sound strategy.
玄峰の音術を熟知する兵士が
組み込まれていた
（金属をたたく音）
（音術兵）あっ これは…
Ah, that's not the signal.
合図の音ではない
秦国兵が鳴らしている音が
混ざっている
There's a sound the State of Qin soldiers are mixing in there... Those bastards.
ヤツらめ…
Send a signal to the sound units to change the bells!
音術隊へ鐘を換えるよう合図を送れ
（部下たち）はっ！
What's this sound?
何じゃ？ この音は
（部下）し… 秦国の騎馬隊！
It's-It's a State of Qin mounted unit!
Watch your backs! State of Wei soldiers are there!
後ろ 気をつけろ！
魏国の兵がいやがるぞ！
Don't stop! Keep moving forward!
止まるな 進め！
This way!
（石）こっちだ
（兵士）続け！
Follow!
（信）ウウッ…
この辺りは煙が濃くなってきてんぞ
The smoke's really thick here.
煙幕の元が近いということです
（信）ヘヘッ…
That means we're close to the source of the smokescreen.
しかし ヤツら この目くらましが
完全に裏目に出やがったな
But this camouflage is totally gonna backfire on them!
I can't wait to see the looks on their faces when we jump out of the smoke!
煙の中から
いきなり俺らが出てきたら―
どんな顔すっか 見ものだぜ！
The only problem remaining is the headquarters' numbers.
あとは やはり 本陣の兵士の数です
着いてみりゃ分かるさ！
We'll know as soon as we get there.
You'll know soon.
すぐに分かるぞ
（信･楚水）えっ？
The headquarters is already...
（石）本陣は もう… 目の前だ
right before our eyes.
ほう…
Fools.
阿呆(あほう)が…
Xin
Lord Xuan Feng, that signal!
（魏兵）玄峰さま あの合図は！
I know!
（玄峰）
分かっておる いちいち言うな
You don't need to tell me every little thing!
Heh. So there are fools that are seriously trying to attack without even knowing what sort of forces we have here?
ほう…
ここの戦力が分からぬうえで―
本気で狙ってくる阿呆がおったか
They probably think they can use this smoke to their advantage to attack us when we're unguarded, but I've seen through it!
せめて この煙を逆手に
虚を突けると思うたであろうが
筒抜けじゃ
My sound units are, of course, also working in our defense.
わしの音術隊は
当然 守りの働きも兼ねておる
Those State of Qin fledglings.
秦国の ひよっこどもが
Now you'll learn.
思い知れ
The headquarters is already right before our eyes!
（石）本陣は もう… 目の前だ
（玄峰）勢いだけでは
戦は ままならぬということを
Momentum alone is not enough to win wars!
Fools.
阿呆が…
Our surprise attack was exposed!
（楚水）奇襲がバレていた！
一度 立て直したほうが…
We'd best regroup for now!
クッ… いや このまま突っ込む！
No, we're going to keep charging ahead! Look!
見ろ！
敵の本陣 数は そんなに多くねえ！
The enemy headquarters' numbers aren't that big!
Understood!
分かりました！
では 信どのは２～３列下がって
前は我々に！
Then Lord Xin, fall back two or three rows! Let us go first!
バカ言え！ 俺が先頭を行くから
みんなが走れるんだろうが！
No way! Everyone's able to run like this because I'm the one taking the lead!
Here we go, Feixin Unit!
（信）いくぞ 飛信隊！
（兵士たち）オーッ！
（廉頗）ほう…
Target the front-most soldier.
先頭の兵を狙わせよ
（部下）ははっ！
Yes, sir.
Lie Brothers, protect the Thousand-Man General!
烈(れつ)兄弟 千人将を！
（烈兄弟）おう！
（信）うん？
余計なことすんな てめえら！
Don't butt in, you guys!
（烈兄）ハハッ…
立場をわきまえぬか 大将！
Do you not know what our positions are, General?!
なに？
What?!
この場で あんたを失えば
我らの全滅は必至！
If we lose you here, our downfall is certain!
（烈弟）そのとおりだ！
That's right!
分かったら
おとなしく 俺たちを盾に使え！
If you understand that, stop trying to fight it and just use us as shields!
You guys...
お前ら…
（烈兄）ハハッ！ 大金はたいて
重装備にした甲斐(かい)があったな 弟よ
Looks like it was worth the money to buy this heavy armor, little brother!
Yeah! C'mon, shoot us with all you've got!
（烈弟）おう！
（烈兄）さあ 射(う)ってこい
魏国のヘボ弓兵どもよ！
You clumsy State of Wei bowmen!
（弓兵隊長）
先頭の騎馬に集中しろ！
Concentrate fire on the leading mounted soldiers!
射て！
Fire!
Get your head down!
頭下げてろ！
（馬のいななき）
ウワッ…
兄者！
（信）おい！
Big Brother!
Hey!
G-Go, Thousand-Man General!
（烈兄）い… 行け！ 千人将…
Big Brother!
（烈弟）兄者！
（指揮官）
く… 来るぞ！ 弓兵 下がれ！
H-Here they come! Bow soldiers, stand back!
Lance soldiers, forward!
槍兵(やりへい) 前へ！
（槍兵たち）オーッ！
（楚水）歩兵が前に出た！
（信）かまうか！ 蹴散らせ！
Foot soldiers have moved forward!
I don't care! Just trample them down!
Here they come!
（槍兵）来るぞ！ 準備は いいか！
All ready?!
Utter fools.
ど阿呆が
Wh-What are those things?!
な… 何だ？ あれは
They were hiding... things like that underground?!
地面に
あんな物が隠してあったのか…
The reason Xuan Feng did not have many soldiers in his headquarters
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）
玄峰本陣の兵が多くなかったのは
それに見合う以上の仕掛けが
用意されていたからである
was because he had tricks setup to compensate for it.
In front of the headquarters was a stake trap for bringing down mounted soldiers.
本陣の前面は 騎兵をしとめる杭(くい)の
ワナが伏せられていた
With the appearance of this trap, the Feixin Unit's vanguard
この仕掛けの出現で―
飛信隊の前方は
僅かな兵を残して ほぼ壊滅
with the exception of a few soldiers, completely wiped out.
後方の仲間たちとも
大きく分断された
It also created a large gap between them and their comrades further back.
As a result, Xin and the others in the front
結果 先頭だった信たちは―
were thrown before Xuan Feng's headquarters of 8,000 soldiers.
玄峰本陣の兵800の前に
放り出される形となったのである
ンンッ！ ひるむな！
敵将の姿は見えてるぞ！
Don't falter!
I can see the enemy general!
You just don't get it, do you?
分かっておらんな
おぬしらのような激情の輩(やから)は
たやすく士気が頂点に達するが
Passionate guys like you may be able to make morale surge easily,
but on the other side of it, when that breaks down, you fall to the deepest despair,
反面 それを砕かれたとき―
失意の底に落ちて
すぐには立ち直れぬ
one you can't recover from quickly.
It is a weakness of soldiers that rely on momentum that has been exposed again and again since ancient times.
勢い頼みの兵のさらけ出す
古来よりの弱点よ
I cannot stand the sight of them. Chop them to pieces!
見るに堪えぬ　切り刻め
楚水！
Chu Shui!
（斬る音）
（飛信隊兵）隊長！
Captain!
Lord Xin!
I can't believe it...
（楚水）
なんということだ こんな所で…
At a place like this...
Then, for only a moment, the direction of the wind changed.
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）そのとき
ほんの一瞬 風向きが変わり
煙幕が
信たちの すぐ後ろまで流れた
And the smokescreen was blown to just behind Xin and the others.
Then, astoundingly...
そして 驚くべきことに
その煙の中から―
the Yufeng Unit appeared from within that smoke!
玉鳳(ぎょくほう)隊が現れたのである
What?!
なに！
This is an embarrassment.
（王賁(おうほん)）恥ずべきことだ
Falling behind someone like you.
（王賁）お前らごときに
後れを取っていたとは
Wang Ben...
王賁…
Forward, Yufeng Unit!
（王賁）進め 玉鳳隊！
余計な敵には目もくれるな！
Pay no attention to any other enemies!
目指す敵将は もう目の前だ！
The enemy general we are after... is right in front of our eyes!
あっ！ ま… 待て てめえら！
W-Wait you guys!
How can this be?! We never got a signal that they would be appearing!
（指揮官）バカな！
ヤツらの出現を
知らせる合図など なかったぞ！
Oh. So they only came once they had seriously eliminated all sound units nearby, eh?
ほう…
生真面目に周囲の音術隊を
始末してから来たか
しかし よく この短時間で…
Though it's pretty impressive they did it so fast.
フッ…
少しは優秀なのが出てきたか
Looks like I may have some pretty good ones on my hands.
く… くそ！
D-Dammit.
（飛信隊兵）隊長！
Captain!
（信）
オッ！ お前ら 無事だったか！
Y-You guys! You're all right?!
We're glad you're okay, too!
（飛信隊兵Ａ）隊長こそ！
Just like the Yufeng Unit did, we used the corpses as footholds to get over the traps.
（飛信隊兵Ｂ）玉鳳隊のように
屍(しかばね)を足場にして越えてきました
よし まだいける！
Okay! We can still do this!
Follow the Yufeng Unit!
玉鳳隊を追うぞ！
We're going to be the ones to take the enemy general's head!
敵将の首を取るのは俺たちだ！
（飛信隊兵たち）オーッ！
（激突音）
（兵士たち）ウワッ！
Pieces of shit.
（盾をたたく音）
くそが… 好き放題やりやがって
They're just doing whatever they want!
音の攪乱は成功してんのか？
Is screwing up the sound signals working?!
クッ… ヤツら
ころころ 音と律を変えてやがる
Those guys are changing their sound and rhythm to something faster and more high-pitched! Now...
これじゃ…
The third unit has been wiped out!
（兵士）第３隊 全滅だ！
Listen closely, Feixin Unit!
聞け 飛信隊！
We need only endure a little longer!
もう少しの辛抱だ！
ここを耐えれば 必ず…
If we can hold out, I'm sure...
I'm sure the captain will return having defeated the enemy general!
必ず 隊長が
敵将を討って帰還される！
Lord Xin...
信どの…
うらぁ！
We caught up to the Yufeng Unit?
（信）玉鳳隊に追いついた？
（楚水）いつもの勢いがない
They don't have their usual momentum.
恐らくは 隊長 王賁の
負傷が影響しているのでしょう
They're probably being affected by their captain, Wang Ben's, wounds.
What? That guy's injured?
（信）なんだ あいつ…
ケガしてやがったのか
（信）
ケッ！ かすり傷ひとつで―
You'd better not go pale from one little scratch, Young Master!
青くなってんじゃねえぞ
お坊ちゃんが！
We might need you as backup support!
てめえらは
俺らの後方支援でもやってな！
（番陽(ばんよう)）クッ… あのガキが！
賁さまの傷の深さも知らずに！
That brat.
He doesn't even know how deep Lord Ben's wound is!
檄(げき)のつもりか？ どこまで恥辱を！
Is he trying to encourage me?!
Just how much is he going to disgrace me?!
Lord Ben!
（番陽）賁さま！
Get in front of Lord Ben!
賁さまが前に！ 続け！ 続けー！
Follow along!
I told you, didn't I?
（玄峰）だから 言っておろうが
If you think a battle can be won as long as you've got momentum, you're dead wrong.
戦が勢いだけで
うまくいくと思ったら大間違いじゃ
（魏兵）第５隊 第６隊 進め！
Fifth unit, sixth unit, forward!
第７隊 第８隊 展開せよ！
Seventh unit, eighth unit, unfold!
Reinforcements to the enemy defense are coming!
敵守備の増援が来ます！
（信）関係ねえ！
It doesn't matter!
The enemy general is right in front of us!
敵将は…
目の前だ！
Enemy reinforcements!
（玉鳳隊兵）敵兵の増援です！
Ignore it! There aren't even that many of them!
（番陽）
かまわん！ 大した数ではない
このまま突き進め！
Keep pushing forward!
There's a sand cloud rising from the enemy headquarters?
（王賁）
敵の本陣に砂煙が上がっている
Are they changing formation?!
何か陣形を変えているのか？
（刺す音）
（楚水）隊長！
Captain!
Bastard!
（信）てめえ！
（斬る音）
いけ！ もう抜けるぞ！
Go! We're almost through!
Lord Xuan Feng, preparations are complete!
（副官）
玄峰さま 準備が整いました！
Be on alert! They're about to pull something!
気をつけろ 何かあるぞ！
Okay...
よし…
retreat.
退却じゃ
に… 逃げた…
Th-They ran?
ど… どういうことだ？
まだ あんなに守りの兵がいるのに
What's going on here?
They've still got so many defensive soldiers.
Is this another one of their traps?!
これも 何かのワナか？
Ring the gong to signal all units to retreat.
（玄峰）全軍に退却のドラを鳴らせ
（副官）ははっ！
Yes, sir!
L-Look!
（番陽）み… 見ろ！
魏国軍全軍がひいていくぞ！
The entire State of Wei Army is retreating!
We... made them retreat.
（玉鳳隊兵）
俺たちが ひかせたんだ…
We did it.
（玉鳳隊兵）やった…
（玉鳳隊兵たち）
やった！ やったぞ！
All right! We did it!
やったぞー！
That strategist, Xuan Feng,
（廉頗）軍略家の玄峰は―
武将特有の意地のようなものは
持ち合わせておらぬ
does not possess the pride typical of military commanders.
詰められれば ひく　それだけじゃ
If he can be cornered, he'll withdraw. That's all this is.
（白亀西(はくきさい)）アア…
Of course, that is generally a decision only made once his job has been fulfilled.
無論 あらかた仕事が済んだという
判断があってのことだがのぅ
If I'm being ambitious, I actually wanted to trample them one more time,
欲を言えば
あとひととき蹂躙(じゅうりん)させたかったが
まあ よかろう　８割方は全うした
but this is fine.
80% is quite respectable.
If I'm too greedy...
あまり欲を出すと…
I might die an early death.
早死にするでな
ハッ… 玄峰さまー！
Lord Xuan Feng!
おらぁ！
I missed...
外した…
Wait, Lord Xin!
（楚水）ま… 待て 信どの！
ムチャは よせ！
Don't be reckless!
（信）ジャマすんな 楚水！
Get out of my way, Chu Shui!
もはや あの将の所まで
刃(やいば)は届きません！
Your blade can no longer reach that general!
それより
敵をひかせただけでも十分だ！
Making the enemy retreat was more than enough!
It's not nearly enough!
ひとつも十分じゃねえ！
What do you mean we made them retreat?
（信）なにが“ひかせた”だ！
Do you know how many died on our side?!
こっちは
どんだけ死んだと思ってんだ！
We were completely...
俺たちは まんまと…
まんまと
あいつに してやられたんだ！
completely beaten by them!
Shit! Shit!
くそ… くそー！
It was just as Xin said.
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）信の言葉どおりであった
When the smokescreen covering the battlefield had cleared,
戦場を覆っていた煙幕が消えたとき
秦国軍は―
the State of Qin Army became aware of the number of dead and were horrified.
その すさまじい死傷者の数に
気づき 愕然(がくぜん)とした
They suffered a massive defeat without even knowing it.
知らぬ間に大敗していたのである
う～む…
State of Qin Army had the wind completely taken out of its sails.
（ﾅﾚｰﾀｰ）秦国軍は 完全に
出ばなをくじかれる形となった
Preview
The Thief VS
The Strategist
End